{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109706437","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109706436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" a24426e1-94f2-41d4-9b87-3661b57d05e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_zo..zo.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_zo_po-two-zo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109718171","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109718171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" bb8b6dd0-e052-4989-8f0a-5003e48343da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" za"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109720810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109720810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" bb8b6dd0-e052-4989-8f0a-5003e48343da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" za"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109722365","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109722365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" bb8b6dd0-e052-4989-8f0a-5003e48343da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ze"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZE"," userResponse":" ZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109725051","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109725051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" bb8b6dd0-e052-4989-8f0a-5003e48343da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ze"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109726501","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109726501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" bb8b6dd0-e052-4989-8f0a-5003e48343da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ze"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109726623","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109726623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" bb8b6dd0-e052-4989-8f0a-5003e48343da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ze"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109739055","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109739055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" za"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109741781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109741781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" za"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109743328","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109743328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ze"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZE"," userResponse":" ZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109746000","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109746000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ze"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109747551","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109747551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZI"," userResponse":" ZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109750198","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109750197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109751758","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109751758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZO"," userResponse":" ZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109754406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109754406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109755963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109755963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZU"," userResponse":" ZU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109758793","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109758793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109760805","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109760805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109760964","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109760964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109771401","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109771401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:zo..zo.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109781677","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109781677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109786646","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109786646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 0295bc39-7f51-4456-bd13-502658cf2d4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.za..zu.asc.lc.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109797251","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109797251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" d28a78d7-5ae7-48c8-b2ba-08f20d5724d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109801792","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109801792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" d28a78d7-5ae7-48c8-b2ba-08f20d5724d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109807223","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109807223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" d28a78d7-5ae7-48c8-b2ba-08f20d5724d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109812314","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109812314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" d28a78d7-5ae7-48c8-b2ba-08f20d5724d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" je"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109817634","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109817634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" d28a78d7-5ae7-48c8-b2ba-08f20d5724d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109824069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109824069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" d28a78d7-5ae7-48c8-b2ba-08f20d5724d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109829254","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109829254"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" d28a78d7-5ae7-48c8-b2ba-08f20d5724d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109833925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109833925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" d28a78d7-5ae7-48c8-b2ba-08f20d5724d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109838176","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109838176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" d28a78d7-5ae7-48c8-b2ba-08f20d5724d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109841808","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109841808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" d28a78d7-5ae7-48c8-b2ba-08f20d5724d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109887113","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109887112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" d28a78d7-5ae7-48c8-b2ba-08f20d5724d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109907480","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109907480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 09ca91a2-f876-4001-aed5-f2136e6ad8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109912383","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109912383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 09ca91a2-f876-4001-aed5-f2136e6ad8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109916782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109916782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 09ca91a2-f876-4001-aed5-f2136e6ad8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109920905","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109920905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 09ca91a2-f876-4001-aed5-f2136e6ad8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109925080","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109925080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 09ca91a2-f876-4001-aed5-f2136e6ad8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109929686","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109929686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 09ca91a2-f876-4001-aed5-f2136e6ad8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" re"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109935546","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109935546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 09ca91a2-f876-4001-aed5-f2136e6ad8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109944856","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109944856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 09ca91a2-f876-4001-aed5-f2136e6ad8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109950455","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109950455"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 09ca91a2-f876-4001-aed5-f2136e6ad8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109954399","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109954399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 09ca91a2-f876-4001-aed5-f2136e6ad8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109959827","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109959827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 09ca91a2-f876-4001-aed5-f2136e6ad8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109963989","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109963989"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 09ca91a2-f876-4001-aed5-f2136e6ad8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109975792","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109975792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 65fb4a44-39a9-4807-8985-c93823fa9318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109979809","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109979809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 65fb4a44-39a9-4807-8985-c93823fa9318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109984111","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109984111"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 65fb4a44-39a9-4807-8985-c93823fa9318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109989390","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109989389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 65fb4a44-39a9-4807-8985-c93823fa9318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109994480","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109994480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 65fb4a44-39a9-4807-8985-c93823fa9318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549109998609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549109998609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 65fb4a44-39a9-4807-8985-c93823fa9318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110004453","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110004453"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 65fb4a44-39a9-4807-8985-c93823fa9318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110008326","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110008326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 65fb4a44-39a9-4807-8985-c93823fa9318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110013373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110013373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 65fb4a44-39a9-4807-8985-c93823fa9318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110017486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110017486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 65fb4a44-39a9-4807-8985-c93823fa9318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110022191","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110022190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 65fb4a44-39a9-4807-8985-c93823fa9318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110027937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110027936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 65fb4a44-39a9-4807-8985-c93823fa9318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110037901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110037901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" 65fb4a44-39a9-4807-8985-c93823fa9318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110058371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110058370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" b6e4b4a3-148c-498c-b49a-f2e3a9b47379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pa_po_pe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110064992","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110064992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" b6e4b4a3-148c-498c-b49a-f2e3a9b47379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pa_po_pe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110071637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110071637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" b6e4b4a3-148c-498c-b49a-f2e3a9b47379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pa_pu_po"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110078280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110078280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" b6e4b4a3-148c-498c-b49a-f2e3a9b47379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_po_pi_pa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110084891","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110084891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" b6e4b4a3-148c-498c-b49a-f2e3a9b47379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pa_po_pe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110091484","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110091484"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" b6e4b4a3-148c-498c-b49a-f2e3a9b47379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pi_pa_pu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110098095","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110098095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" b6e4b4a3-148c-498c-b49a-f2e3a9b47379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_po_pu_pa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110104705","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110104705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" b6e4b4a3-148c-498c-b49a-f2e3a9b47379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_po_pa_pe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110111334","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110111333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" b6e4b4a3-148c-498c-b49a-f2e3a9b47379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pu_pa_pe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110117948","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110117948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" b6e4b4a3-148c-498c-b49a-f2e3a9b47379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pe_po_pa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110131128","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110131128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" b6e4b4a3-148c-498c-b49a-f2e3a9b47379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_pe_po_pa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110155061","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110155061"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pa_po_pe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110162528","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110162528"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pa_po_pe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110169138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110169137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pa_po_pe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110175766","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110175766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pa_pu_po"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110182394","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110182394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_po_pi_pa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110189025","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110189025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pa_po_pe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110195632","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110195632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pi_pa_pu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110202242","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110202242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_po_pu_pa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110208870","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110208870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_po_pa_pe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110215498","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110215498"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pu_pa_pe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110222127","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110222127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pe_po_pa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110235190","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110235189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_pe_po_pa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110243900","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110243899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_pe_po_pa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110255879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110255879"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_pe_po_pa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.pa..pu.asc.lc.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110268034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110268034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_151459"," gameId":" c6e0e776-898f-42a3-94a7-9c1a362b42d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.pa..pa.noShow..14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_pe_po_pa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}